

UX & UI Design, Front-end Development.

Profile

Digital Product Designer and Front-end Developer from London. I design and build websites and design systems for individuals, small businesses and startups. I currently live between London and Hamburg.

Expertise

- User Interface Design Sketching,
 Wireframing, Designing Web and Mobile applications. Building design systems in Sketch, Figma and Framer X.
- User Experience Design User Research,
 User Task Flows, Site Mapping, Persona
 Creation, Wireframing.
- Visual Identity Design, Icon Design.
- Front-end Prototyping using Static Site
 Generators Hugo and Gatsby.
- Building Front-end Component Libraries.
- Writing scaleable CSS architecture SUITCSS, SMACSS, OOCSS, ITCSS.
- Web Typography working with modular scales, responsive and fluid type systems and variable fonts.

Experience

UX & UI Design. Front-end development

Angel Investment Network, London

Oct 2014 - Present

Userflow design. Sketching and wireframing. Hi-fidelity prototyping. Designing and building front-end design systems: ainlabs.netlify.com. Brand Identity Design.

Web Design & Development

Harvey Nichols, London

Oct 2011 - April 2015

Editorial design for print and web. Photographic retouching & image manipulation.

Web & Editoral Design

Avenue 32, London

Feb 2013 - Jul 2013

Editorial design for print and web. Photographic retouching & image manipulation.

Web Design & Front-end Development

SampsonMay Design Ltd, London

Feb 2011 - April 2011

Website design and development. HTML and CSS prototyping.

Personal Projects

In Detail

Co-founder / UX & UI Designer

Feb 2011 - Present

In Detail is an online jewellery publication with a unique and accessible perspective on the international jewellery industry. The brand hosts regular events in partnership with Soho House and offers an engagement ring concierge service for couples.

indtl.com

Type Services

Typography Design
Feb 2017 - Present

Type Services is a type design practice offering free and premium fonts. The project explores imperfection and inconsistency in type design, and is the result of my lifelong fascination with letterforms.

typeservices.co

Education

University of the Arts London

Diplomas in Graphic Design

Jan 2008 - Mar 2018

Design for Visual Communication, Desktop Publishing, Design & Layout Skills, Pixel and Vector Based Image Manipulation.

University of Leeds

BA(Hons) Fine Art & History of Art

Sept 2004 - Sept 2007

Study of the New York School & Sculpture and the Object. 3 year painting & screenprinting practice. My dissertation explores the impact of technology on creating artwork.

Technical Skills

Software	Languages	Tools
Figma	HTML5	Git
Framer X	CSS3	Abstract
Sketch	SCSS	Gulp
Adobe Suite	Ajax	Webpack
VS Code	JavaScript	Pen & paper
Wordpress	React	
Hugo	Node	
Gatsby		
Contentful		